Guide to the George A. Romero Archival Collection, 1962-2017 SC.2019.03
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- Scripts, circa 1964-2017; I.
  - Unproduced Works, circa 1964-2013; 2.
    - The Girl Who Loved Tom Gordon, 1999-2005; 39.
      - The Girl Who Loved Tom Gordon includes letter and annotations by Stephen King, June 14, 1999 (Box 35, Folder 2)
      - The Girl Who Loved Tom Gordon third draft, May 10, 2001 (Box 35, Folder 3)
      - The Girl Who Loved Tom Gordon, circa 2001 (Box 35, Folder 4)
      - The Girl Who Loved Tom Gordon, 2005 (Box 35, Folder 5)
      - The Girl Who Loved Tom Gordon, circa 2005 (Box 35, Folder 6)
      - The Girl Who Loved Tom Gordon (post-it noting "New Version"), circa 2005 (Box 35, Folder 7)
    - The Giver, December 14, 2004; 40.
      - The Giver by Todd Alcott, December 14, 2004 (Box 36, Folder 1)
    - Gogiro (Loves You), undated; 41.
      - Gogiro (Loves You) by Mark Jacobson, undated (Box 36, Folder 2)
    - Golem, circa 1995-1996; 42.
      - Golem first draft, February 1995 (Box 36, Folder 3)
      - Golem second draft (copy 1), February 1996 (Box 36, Folder 4)
      - Golem second draft (copy 2), February 1996 (Box 36, Folder 5)
      - Golem draft script (48 pages), undated (Box 36, Folder 6)
      - Golem draft script (120 pages), undated (Box 36, Folder 7)
    - Goosebumps, undated; 43.
      - Goosebumps treatment, undated (Box 36, Folder 8)
      - Goosebumps (full copy, 2 partial scripts containing possible revisions, fax about project), March 19, 1996 (Box 36, Folder 9)
    - G.P.S., undated; 44.
      - G.P.S., undated (Box 37, Folder 1)
    - Gunperson, 1978; 45.
      - Gunperson, 1978 (Box 37, Folder 2)
    - Hell, August 22, 1995; 46.
      - Hell first draft (copy 1), August 22, 1995 (Box 37, Folder 3)
      - Hell first draft (copy 2), August 22, 1995 (Box 37, Folder 4)
      - Hell first draft (copy 3), August 22, 1995 (Box 37, Folder 5)
      - Hell first draft (copy 4), August 22, 1995 (Box 37, Folder 6)
    - Hell Hotel [Hell Bent] [Hot-L Diablo], circa 1995; 47.
      - Hell Hotel first draft (copy 1), December 1995 (Box 37, Folder 7)
      - Hell Hotel first draft (copy 2), December 1995 (Box 37, Folder 8)
      - Hell Hotel (48 pages), undated (Box 37, Folder 9)
      - Hell Hotel (58 pages), undated (Box 37, Folder 10)
      - Hell Hotel [Hot-L Diablo] treatment, undated (Box 38, Folder 1)
      - Hell Hotel [Hell Bent] (copy 1), undated (Box 38, Folder 2)
      - Hell Hotel [Hell Bent] (copy 2), undated (Box 38, Folder 3)
    - Hoffman through the Mansions of the Moon [Hoffman: Through the Mansions of the Moon], circa 1985; 48.
      - Hoffman: Through the Mansions of the Moon (copy 1), 1985 (Box 38, Folder 4)
      - Hoffman: Through the Mansions of the Moon (copy 2), 1985 (Box 38, Folder 5)
      - Hoffman: Through the Mansions of the Moon (copy 3), undated (Box 38, Folder 6)
    - Honus, undated; 49.
      - Honus treatment or story, undated (Box 38, Folder 7)
    - House with a Clock in its Walls, undated; 50.
      - House with a Clock in its Walls (2 copies), undated (Box 38, Folder 8)
      - House with a Clock in its Walls (pages 9-14), undated (Box 38, Folder 9)
      - House with a Clock in its Walls (includes possible prologue titled "Good and Evil"), undated (Box 38, Folder 10)
      - House with a Clock in its Walls (multiple drafts, incomplete parts, and revisions includes "Good and Evil" Prologue), undated (Box 38, Folder 11)
      - House with a Clock in its Walls treatment, undated (Box 38, Folder 12)
      - House with a Clock in its Walls treatment, undated (Box 38, Folder 13)
    - It, circa 1989; 51.
      - It Part 1 by Lawrence Cohen, January 12, 1989 (Box 39, Folder 1)
      - It Part 2 by Lawrence Cohen, April 1, 1989 (Box 39, Folder 2)
      - It Part 3 by Lawrence Cohen, June 8, 1989 (Box 39, Folder 3)
      - It script overview and treatment marked "Much Ado About It", undated (Box 39, Folder 4)
    - Jack and the Beanstalk, 52.
      - Jack and the Beanstalk, undated (Box 39, Folder 5)
    - Knightriders II: the Rival for Camelot, 2002; 53.
      - Knightriders II: the Rival for Camelot by V.R. Franko, 2002 (Box 39, Folder 6)
    - The Lord of the Rings: The Fellowship of the Ring, 2001; 54.
      - The Lord of the Rings: The Fellowship of the Ring by Fran Walsh, Philippa Boyens, and Peter Jackson, 2001 (Box 39, Folder 7)
    - Mad House, undated; 55.
      - Mad House, undated (Box 39, Folder 8)
    - Mannequin, February 14 2003; 56.
      - Mannequin revised script (copy 1), February 14, 2003 (Box 39, Folder 9)
      - Mannequin revised script (copy 2), February 14, 2003 (Box 40, Folder 1)
      - Mannequin revised script (copy 3), February 14, 2003 (Box 40, Folder 2)
    - Masque of the Red Death, circa 1989; 57.
      - Masque of the Red Death first draft, February 1989 (Box 40, Folder 3)
      - Masque of the Red Death draft script (81 pages), undated (Box 40, Folder 4)
      - Masque of the Red Death draft script (80 pages), undated (Box 40, Folder 5)
    - Meat Markets, 1993; 58.
      - Meat Markets by Guillermo del Toro, 1993 (Box 40, Folder 6)
    - Mickey B., undated; 59.
      - Mickey B. draft script, undated (Box 40, Folder 7)
    - Midnight Show, circa 1998; 60.
      - Midnight Show treatment (incomplete, missing pages 21-33), October 19, 1998 (Box 40, Folder 8)
      - Midnight Show treatment second draft, November 3, 1998 (Box 40, Folder 9)
      - Midnight Show script (incomplete, ends on page 27), undated (Box 40, Folder 10)
      - Midnight Show script, undated (Box 40, Folder 11)
    - Monster MASH, 1996; 61.
      - Monster MASH treatment (2 copies), 1996 (Box 40, Folder 12)
    - Monster Movie, 62.
      - Monster Movie story synopsis (2 copies), undated (Box 40, Folder 13)
    - Moonshadows, circa 1997; 63.
      - Moonshadows partial first draft, ends on page 71, March 21, 1997 (Box 41, Folder 1)
      - Moonshadows first draft, March 21, 1997 (Box 41, Folder 2)
      - Moonshadows first draft, March 27, 1997 (Box 41, Folder 3)
      - Moonshadows draft script, undated (Box 41, Folder 4)
      - Moonshadows third draft (copy 1), September 1997 (Box 41, Folder 5)
      - Moonshadows third draft (copy 2), September 1997 (Box 41, Folder 6)
      - Moonshadows third draft (copy 3), September 1997 (Box 41, Folder 7)
      - Moonshadows third draft (copy 4), September 1997 (Box 41, Folder 8)
    - Mountain Man, undated; 64.
      - Mountain Man (3 copies) treatment/proposal for TV film or series, undated (Box 42, Folder 1)
    - The Mummy and Return of the Mummy [1980s], undated; 65.
      - The Mummy and Return of the Mummy script (copy 1), undated (Box 42, Folder 2)
      - The Mummy and Return of the Mummy script (copy 2), undated (Box 42, Folder 3)
      - The Mummy and Return of the Mummy script (copy 3), undated (Box 42, Folder 4)
      - The Mummy and Return of the Mummy script (copy 4), undated (Box 42, Folder 5)
      - The Mummy and Return of the Mummy script (copy 5), undated (Box 42, Folder 6)
      - The Mummy and Return of the Mummy script (copy 6), undated (Box 42, Folder 7)
    - The Mummy [1990s], circa 1993-1994; 66.
      - The Mummy by Alan Ormsby rewrite by John Sayles, 1993 (Box 42, Folder 8)
      - The Mummy script, undated (Box 42, Folder 9)
      - The Mummy script, August 3, 1994 (Box 42, Folder 10)
      - The Mummy second draft, August 3, 1994 (Box 42, Folder 11)
    - Murderer, May 20, 1983; 67.
      - Murderer by Anthony Shaffer, May 20, 1983 (Box 43, Folder 1)
    - Naked Jungle, undated; 68.
      - Naked Jungle, undated (Box 43, Folder 2)
    - Native Tongue, 1994-1995; 69.
      - Native Tongue by Ed Harris rewrite by George A. Romero (copy 1), April 1994 (Box 43, Folder 3)
      - Native Tongue by Ed Harris rewrite by George A. Romero (copy 2), April 1994 (Box 43, Folder 4)
      - Native Tongue by Ed Harris rewrite by George A. Romero (copy 3), April 1994 (Box 43, Folder 5)
      - Native Tongue second draft by Ed Harris and George A. Romero (copy 1), March 1995 (Box 43, Folder 6)
      - Native Tongue second draft by Ed Harris and George A. Romero (copy 2), March 1995 (Box 43, Folder 7)
    - Necronauts, undated; 70.
      - Necronauts proposed outline (2 copies), undated (Box 43, Folder 8)
    - Necronomicon, undated; 71.
      - Necronomicon draft script, undated (Box 43, Folder 9)
    - News, undated; 72.
      - News, undated (Box 43, Folder 10)
    - Night of the Living Dead: The Series, October 1997; 73.
      - Night of the Living Dead: The Series treatment/outline for TV series comprised of 19 episodes first draft, October 1997 (Box 43, Folder 11)
    - Nuns from Outer Space, April 8, 1998; 74.
      - Nuns from Outer Space treatment for TV series first draft, April 8, 1998 (Box 43, Folder 12)
    - Outpost #5, undated; 75.
      - Outpost #5 printed from defunct website, written in prose, possible short story, undated (Box 43, Folder 13)
    - Pay the Piper, undated; 76.
      - Pay the Piper unfinished novel manuscript draft (2 folders), undated (Box 44, Folder 1-2)
    - Pet Sematary, 1984-1985; 77.
      - Pet Sematary by Stephen King first draft, November 15, 1984 (Box 44, Folder 3)
      - Pet Sematary by Stephen King revised draft (copy 1), April 15, 1985 (Box 44, Folder 4)
      - Pet Sematary by Stephen King revised draft (copy 2), April 15, 1985 (Box 44, Folder 5)
      - Pet Sematary by Stephen King revised draft (copy 3), April 15, 1985 (Box 44, Folder 6)
    - Peter and the Wolfman, June 22, 1998; 78.
      - Peter and the Wolfman treatment for IMAX 3-D film first draft, June 22, 1998 (Box 44, Folder 7)
    - Peterstein, undated; 79.
      - Peterstein "basic premise for a film" by S. William Hinzman and George A. Romero, undated (Box 44, Folder 8)
    - Phobophilia [Bandit at Twelve O'Clock], July 29, 1993; 80.
      - Phobophilia [Bandit at Twelve O'Clock] with overview and letter to Penn Jillette (2 copies of script), July 29, 1993 (Box 44, Folder 9)
    - The Power, undated; 81.
      - The Power short story, undated (Box 45, Folder 1)
      - The Power draft script, undated (Box 45, Folder 2)
      - The Power script with short overview/pitch for series, undated (Box 45, Folder 3)
      - The Power script, undated (Box 45, Folder 4)
    - Princeton Principle, undated; 82.
      - Princeton Principle short story, undated (Box 45, Folder 5)
    - The Projectionist, April 23, 2002; 83.
      - The Projectionist script for a television pilot, with letter to Michael Carrazza, April 23, 2002 (Box 45, Folder 6)
    - Purgastory [Purgastories], undated; 84.
      - Purgastory [Purgastories] treatment by George A. Romero and Jerry Golod, undated (Box 45, Folder 7)
    - Quevira, circa 1993; 85.
      - Quevira by William B. Farmer 2nd draft, September 4, 1993 (Box 45, Folder 8)
      - Quevira draft script (copy 1), undated (Box 45, Folder 9)
      - Quevira draft script (copy 2), undated (Box 45, Folder 10)
      - Quevira draft script (copy 3), undated (Box 45, Folder 11)
    - The Raven, 1995-1997; 86.
      - The Raven (original) treament for teleplay second draft, October 1995 (Box 45, Folder 12)
      - The Raven teleplay first draft, July 1996 (Box 45, Folder 13)
      - The Raven teleplay first draft, July 21, 1996 (Box 46, Folder 1)
      - The Raven teleplay second draft, October 14, 1996 (Box 46, Folder 2)
      - The Raven teleplay third draft, November 14, 1996 (Box 46, Folder 3)
      - The Raven teleplay revised (copy 1), June 1997 (Box 46, Folder 4)
      - The Raven teleplay revised (copy 2), June 1997 (Box 46, Folder 5)
    - The Recipe, undated; 87.
      - The Recipe, undated (Box 46, Folder 6)
    - Resident Evil, 1997-1998; 88.
      - Resident Evil by Alan McElroy first draft, May 29, 1997 (Box 46, Folder 7)
      - Resident Evil storyline by George A. Romero and Peter Grunwald, August 1998 (Box 46, Folder 8)
      - Resident Evil screenplay by George A. Romero first draft, September 29, 1998 (Box 46, Folder 9)
      - Resident Evil screenplay by George A. Romero first draft, October 5, 1998 (Box 46, Folder 10)
      - Resident Evil screenplay by George A. Romero first draft (copy 1), October 7, 1998 (Box 46, Folder 11)
      - Resident Evil screenplay by George A. Romero first draft (copy 2), October 7, 1998 (Box 46, Folder 12)
      - Resident Evil screenplay, undated (Box 47, Folder 1)
    - Riders of the Purple Sage, August 31, 1986; 89.
      - Riders of the Purple Sage by Gill Dennis first draft, August 31, 1986 (Box 47, Folder 2)
    - Rules of Engagement, undated; 90.
      - Rules of Engagement historical novel or work manuscript draft (2 folders), undated (Box 47, Folder 3-4)
    - Scarecrow, undated; 91.
      - Scarecrow by Joe Ferullo, undated (Box 47, Folder 5)
    - Scream of Fear, April 5, 1994; 92.
      - Scream of Fear treatment and overview (fax cover sheet dated), April 5, 1994 (Box 47, Folder 6)
    - Seeing Things, March 5, 1997; 93.
      - Seeing Things treatment for TV series based on Shirley Jackson stories overview and draft script, March 5, 1997 (Box 47, Folder 7)
    - Shadowman, circa 1997; 94.
      - Shadowman treatment, undated (Box 47, Folder 8)
      - Shadowman screenplay second draft with proposal and appendix, February 5, 1997 (Box 47, Folder 9)
    - Shop Till You Drop [Shop Till You Drop ... Dead], circa 1997; 95.
      - Shop Till You Drop [Shop Till You Drop ... Dead] treatment by George A. Romero based on idea by Jerry Golod, undated (Box 47, Folder 10)
      - Shop Till You Drop treatment first draft, October 1997 (Box 47, Folder 11)
    - The Shotgunners, March 23, 1983; 96.
      - The Shotgunners by Stephen King, March 23, 1983 (Box 47, Folder 12)
        King has stated in interviews that this screenplay was in part reworked for his 1996 novel The Regulators published under his psedonym Richard Bachman
    - Something for Everyone, undated; 97.
      - Something for Everyone treatment, undated (Box 47, Folder 13)
    - Something Outside, circa 1998; 98.
      - Something Outside treatment, undated (Box 47, Folder 14)
      - Something Outside treatment based on Richard Matheson story third draft, August 4, 1998 (Box 47, Folder 15)
    - Spirit Moves [Spirits Move], 1993; 99.
      - Spirit Moves [Spirits Move] by Guillermo del Toro, 1993 (Box 48, Folder 1)
      - Spirit Moves [Spirits Move] by Guillermo del Toro, 1993 (Box 48, Folder 2)
    - The Stand, circa 1984; 100.
      - The Stand by Stephen King, undated (Box 48, Folder 3)
      - The Stand by Stephen King, April 1, 1984 (Box 48, Folder 4)
    - Star West, undated; 101.
      - Star West treatment for possible TV series with episode titles, undated (Box 48, Folder 5)
    - Stray, undated; 102.
      - Stray draft treatment (2 copies), undated (Box 48, Folder 6)
    - Three at a Time, undated; 103.
      - Three at a Time (25 pages), undated (Box 48, Folder 7)
      - Three at a Time (45 pages), undated (Box 48, Folder 8)
    - Turn of the Screw, 1987; 104.
      - Turn of the Screw by Michael Hirst first draft, August 10, 1987 (Box 48, Folder 9)
      - Turn of the Screw by Michael Hirst initial draft, October 7, 1987 (Box 48, Folder 10)
    - Tusk [Tusks], 2003; 105.
      - Tusk (copy 1), undated (Box 48, Folder 11)
      - Tusk (copy 2), undated (Box 48, Folder 12)
      - Tusk, March 11 2003 (Box 49, Folder 1)
      - Tusk, 2003 (Box 49, Folder 2)
      - Tusk [Tusks], 2003 (Box 49, Folder 3)
    - Twilight of the Dead, undated; 106.
      - Twilight of the Dead, includes page of response and notes, undated (Box 49, Folder 4)
    - Unholy Fire, 1992-1993; 107.
      - Unholy Fire by Whitley Strieber, October 2, 1992 (Box 49, Folder 5)
      - Unholy Fire by Whitley Strieber, includes memo and religious pamphlet, October 2, 1992 (Box 49, Folder 6)
      - Unholy Fire by Whitley Strieber first draft, November 25, 1992 (Box 49, Folder 7)
      - Unholy Fire by Whitley Strieber draft 2 (copy 1), May 21, 1993 (Box 49, Folder 8)
      - Unholy Fire by Whitley Strieber draft 2 (copy 2), May 21, 1993 (Box 49, Folder 9)
    - Walla, undated; 108.
      - Walla short story, undated (Box 50, Folder 1)
      - Walla chapter one of unfinished novel, undated (Box 50, Folder 2)
    - War of the Worlds: The Night They Came, 1986; 109.
      - War of the Worlds: The Night They Came first draft (copy 1), June 1986 (Box 50, Folder 3)
      - War of the Worlds: The Night They Came first draft (copy 2), August 1986 (Box 50, Folder 4)
      - War of the Worlds: The Night They Came first draft (copy 3), August 1986 (Box 50, Folder 5)
      - War of the Worlds: The Night They Came first draft (copy 4), August 1986 (Box 50, Folder 6)
      - War of the Worlds: The Night They Came first draft (copy 5), August 1986 (Box 50, Folder 7)
      - War of the Worlds: The Night They Came first draft (copy 6), August 1986 (Box 50, Folder 8)
      - War of the Worlds: The Night They Came second draft, December 1986 (Box 51, Folder 1)
        Includes concept drawings.
    - Whine of the Faun, circa 1964; 110.
      - Whine of the Faun by Rudolph Ricci and George A. Romero, circa 1964 (Box 51, Folder 2)
    - Whiz Kid [Whiz], February 1986; 111.
      - Whiz Kid first draft (122 pages) (copy 1), February 1986 (Box 51, Folder 3)
      - Whiz Kid first draft (122 pages) (copy 2), February 1986 (Box 51, Folder 4)
      - Whiz Kid first draft (122 pages) (copy 3), February 1986 (Box 51, Folder 5)
      - Whiz Kid first draft (122 pages) (copy 4), February 1986 (Box 51, Folder 6)
      - Whiz Kid [Whiz] first draft (148 pages), February 1986 (Box 52, Folder 1)
    - The Zombie Autopsies, circa 2013; 112.
      - The Zombie Autopsies by George A. Romero based on novel by Steven Schlozman incomplete first draft script, June 5, 2013 (Box 52, Folder 2)
      - The Zombie Autopsies incomplete draft script, undated (Box 52, Folder 3)
      - The Zombie Autopsies major events overview and script notes, undated (Box 52, Folder 4)
    - George A. Romero's Zombisodes [Zombisodes] [Zomboid], circa 2006; 113.
      - George A. Romero's Zombisodes [Zomboid] teleplay for episodes 1-18 second draft, April 10, 2006 (Box 52, Folder 5)
      - Zomboid [Zombisodes] incomplete draft script (73 pages), undated (Box 52, Folder 6)
      - Zomboid [Zombisodes] draft script (112 pages), undated (Box 52, Folder 7)
      - Zomboid [Zombisodes] draft script (86 pages), undated (Box 52, Folder 8)
    - Untitled Stories or Treatments [Early Writings], undated; 114.
      - Untitled Story or Treatment begins "Grundy is white...", undated (Box 52, Folder 9)
      - Untitled Story or Treatment begins "Fade up slowly..." includes letter from John Russo commenting on "Phony Flick", undated (Box 52, Folder 10)
      - Untitled Story or Treatment begins "It had rained hard...", undated (Box 52, Folder 11)
      - Untitled Story or Treatment begins "The afternoon is not a bright one", undated (Box 52, Folder 12)
      - Untitled Story or Treatment begins "Buckingham was having a dream", undated (Box 52, Folder 13)
    - Reference Materials, 115.
      Copies of stories and commentary potentially used for project ideas. Also includes scholarly papers pertaining to Romero's work.
      - "The Bell Witch" chapter from Poltergeists: hauntings and the haunted by David C. Knight, 1972 (Box 53, Folder 1)
      - The Golem play by H. Leivick, 1921 (Box 53, Folder 2)
      - The Great Pursuit by Herbert Molloy Mason, Jr. photocopy, 1970 (Box 53, Folder 3)
      - Copies of short stories by Shirley Jackson including "The Smoking Room", "Come to the Fair", "Lord of the Castle", "The Story We Used to Tell", "Journey with a Lady", "The Order of Charlotte's Going", "What a Thought", "Home", and "The Bus" (Box 53, Folder 4)
      - The Movie Rating System by Jack Valenti (Box 53, Folder 5)
      - Commentary about On the Magic Island by W.B. Seabrook by JMorrison from his blog The Nonist, June 29, 2008 (Box 53, Folder 6)
      - "Political Representations within George A Romero's 'Dead' Trilogy" a research proposal and paper by Joseph Thomas, undated (Box 53, Folder 7)
      - "The Sociology of George A. Romero's Dawn of the Dead" research paper by Matt Blazi, December 4, 2001 (Box 53, Folder 8)
      - Sounding by Hank Searls photocopy (copy 1), 1982 (Box 53, Folder 9)
      - Sounding by Hank Searls photocopy (copy 2), 1982 (Box 53, Folder 10)
      - Tales of Hoffman souvenir program from London Films (Box 53, Folder 11)
      - Tales of Hoffman liner notes and libretto from Swiss production published by Decca Record Company Limited, 1978 (Box 53, Folder 12)
      - "Uncle Otto's Truck" by Stephen King, undated (Box 53, Folder 13)
        Undated draft of short story by Stephen King originally published in October 1983 issue of Yankee and later collected in Skeleton Crew (1985)
- Production Materials, circa 1962-2008; II.
  This series contains materials related to the development, production, financing, and distribution of films, television series, advertisements, comic books, and literary prose. This includes correspondence (including some script revisions when included with correspondence), contracts, shooting schedules and shot lists, storyboards, fundraising materials, cast and crew lists, budget documents, and production binders. This series is divided into produced works and unproduced works.
  - Produced Works, circa 1962-2008; 1.
    This subseries contains materials related to the development, production, financing, and distribution of films, television series, advertisements, comic books, and literary prose produced by George A. Romero. This includes correspondence (including some script revisions when included with correspondence), contracts, shooting schedules and shot lists, storyboards, fundraising materials, cast and crew lists, budget documents, and production binders.
    - Expostulations, circa 1962-1964; 1.
      A lost feature film comprised of five short films directed by George A. Romero, Rudolph Ricci, and Richard Ricci.
      - Expostulations promotional fundraising booklet (6 copies), circa 1962-1964 (Box 54, Folder 1)
    - Night of the Living Dead [1968], 1967-2000; 2.
      A horror film about a small group of people attempting to survive in a remote farmhouse as the dead rise to feed on the living around them. Shot in Evans City, PA and Pittsburgh. The film was known as Night of the Anubis and then as Night of the Flesh Eaters during production before being retitled Night of the Living Dead by the distributor. Starring Duane Jones, Judith O'Dea, Marilyn Eastman, Karl Hardman, Judith Ridley, Keith Wayne. Written by John A. Russo and George A. Romero, directed by George A. Romero.
      - Night of the Living Dead materials, 1967-1968 (Box 54, Folder 2)
        Contact info, handwritten notes, list of locations for crawl.
      - Night of the Living Dead copyright certificate [photocopy], October 3, 1979 (Box 54, Folder 3)
      - Night of the Living Dead home video documents, 1988-2000 (Box 54, Folder 4)
        Correspondence, contracts, and other materials regarding video releases of the 1968 Night of the Living Dead.
      - The Latent Image binder, circa 1968-1970 (Box 54, Folder 5)
        Contains contact info, WRS motion picture laboratory info, and notes from Night of the Living Dead and There's Always Vanilla.
    - There's Always Vanilla [At Play with the Angels], 1969; 3.
      - At Play with the Angels: A Motion Picture Investment booklet, 1969 (Box 54, Folder 6)
    - The Crazies, April 29, 1976; 4.
      - The Crazies inquiry letter from Richard Rubinstein to CBS television, April 29, 1976 (Box 54, Folder 7)
    - The Amusement Park, 1973-2019; 5.
      - The Amusement Park materials, 1973-2019 (Box 54, Folder 8)
    - A & P Commercials, June 1975; 6.
      Materials for the production of commercials for A&P markets.
      - Production materials, June 1975 (Box 54, Folder 9)